<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#citySec</title>
    <link>https://citysec.nyc/</link>
    <description>Recent content on #citySec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>

	<atom:link href="https://citysec.nyc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


    <item>
      <title>meeting_01</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/post/2018-09-27-meeting-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/post/2018-09-27-meeting-01/</guid>
      <description>Meeting 1 Recap 🎉 We started out by covering some pros &amp;amp; cons for different linux distros. The main ideas were that Ubuntu is a great daily driver while still learning the nuances of linux. Ubuntu allows you to explore the depths of linux while still offering a safe haven to return to when things get scary. 😱 It may be tempting to jump straight into Arch or Kali linux when practicing web security, but it&amp;rsquo;s more important to use your new favorite OS as your default computer and not as a specialty app that you just need for some wifi cracking.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>things_to_come</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/post/2018-08-22-things-to-come/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/post/2018-08-22-things-to-come/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://citysec.nyc/img/things-to-come-stars-300.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;things to come soon&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-inaugural-meeting&#34;&gt;The Inaugural Meeting 🤓&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope you&amp;rsquo;ll join us for our ☝️ 1st meeting on &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday, September 26th at 6:30pm&lt;/strong&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;ll announce the meeting location on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://join.slack.com/t/citysecnyc/shared_invite/enQtMzk1NTcyMDQxODkwLTY1NmE2MDZkZjJhZWIxNGNmNWVjMjUwNDc3M2I3YmRiYmQ0NDBlMjk0Zjc4MzNhY2JiYjUzMWNmYTE0MjkyYzI&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/page/about/</guid>
      <description>what we be about citySec was formed in the summer of 2018 to provide an ongoing outlet for the growing cybersecurity demand and presence at City College.
citySec is a collective of cybersecurity enthusiasts. 💻
citySec is for everyone. 👥
citySec is fun&amp;hellip; 🎡
so have fun with it! 🎉
contact Please join our slack channel</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>careers</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/page/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/page/careers/</guid>
      <description> internships  NCC Group * opens late in December Trail of Bits Mozilla Google MITRE Fireeye Outreachy * open source Google Summer of Code * open source Facebook PayPal Coinbase  interview prep (behavioral)  Questions to Ask in a Interview  </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>events</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/page/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/page/events/</guid>
      <description> hack with us weekly meeting info (TBD) hack with the community nyc chapter meetings  2600 Empire Hacking NYSEC New York CryptoParty Network DEFCON201 NCC Group Security Forum  conferences (presentations are recorded and published on YouTube)  HOPE BSidesNYC SummerCon CSAW * free THOTCon * got a great deal for students  hackerspaces  NYC Resistor  </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>projects</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/page/projects/</guid>
      <description> NetSec AppSec Hardware Hacking ~ Embedded Systems Reverse Engineering Social Engineering Malware Analysis Cryptography Machine Learning </description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>resources</title>
      <link>https://citysec.nyc/page/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>https://citysec.nyc/page/resources/</guid>
      <description> the hacker way  Build a Successful Career in Infosec Become a Hacker Become a Bug Bounty Hunter Security Roles Get into Security Engineering  protect your data  Check if you&amp;rsquo;ve been compromised in a data breach protect yourself and your data online  blogs  #hacking on Medium  decryption tools  collection of online decryption tools hash cracker  guides  codepath web security guide trail of bits&amp;rsquo; ctf guide nyc infosec Cybrary  hacking practice  ctf time hack this site hackerone - bug bounties metasploitable3 vulnhub OverTheWire CTF List  </description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
